[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these methods is a reliable way to distinguish a natural pearl from a cultured one and a fake one?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Rubbing the pearl on ones teeth", "X-ray examination", "Microscopic examination"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What long-running radio and television police drama was created by and starred Jack Webb?", "correct_answer": "Dragnet", "incorrect_answers": ["Desperate Housewives", "Deadwood", "Dynasty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the state motto of Colorado?", "correct_answer": "Nothing Without the Deity", "incorrect_answers": ["The people rule", "God enriches", "We Dare Defend Our Rights"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "High, low, jack, and game are the four possible points in what trick-taking game?", "correct_answer": "Pitch", "incorrect_answers": ["Pinochle", "Whist", "Bridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Latin American country did the Chihuahua dog breed originate?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Cuba", "Guatemala", "Nicaragua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does about 90 % of volcanic activity on Earth occur?", "correct_answer": "Under the oceans", "incorrect_answers": ["Near the equator", "Alaska", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tegucigalpa is the capital and largest city of this country.", "correct_answer": "Honduras", "incorrect_answers": ["Namibia", "Uzbekistan", "Laos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1988 movie contains this quote: Ive often thought that there should be beauty contests for the *insides* of bodies.?", "correct_answer": "Dead Ringers", "incorrect_answers": ["Puppetmaster", "Dr. Caligari", "The Serpent and the Rainbow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What eminent musician released his album The Fox in 1981?", "correct_answer": "Elton John", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Johnes", "Barry White", "Julio Iglesias"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saturday Night Fever, this actress portrayed the aloof Stephanie Mangano, who after much urging, agreed to be Tony Maneros partner in a dance competition.", "correct_answer": "Karen Gorney", "incorrect_answers": ["Donna Pescow", "Fran Drescher", "Ellen Travolta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What statement is true about the precious stone opal?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["White and green opals are the most common.", "It is a mineraloid gel.", "It usually contains about 3-10% water."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinchillas are great pets for children - they are animals of very friendly nature and love to be held.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]